<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy">
<meta name="description" content="<p>&quot;Sleek Web Designs offers expert SEO services to boost your online visibility, drive traffic, and enhance rankings. Transform your websites performance today!&quot;</p><p>Boost your business with NYC SEO Experts. Achieve higher rankings and growth through expert strategies tailored for success.</p><p>&quot;Discover top New York SEO services for boosting local and national visibility. Achieve online success with expert strategies tailored to your business needs.&quot;</p><p>Boost your online visibility with NYCs top SEO agency. Expert strategies to enhance your digital presence and drive results.</p><p>&quot;Boost your online presence with expert Data-Driven SEO Services in NYC. Achieve top rankings and enhanced visibility tailored to your business needs.&quot;</p><p>Elevate your NYC business with Premier SEO Solutions. Boost visibility, drive traffic, and enhance growth with expert strategies tailored for the Big Apple.</p><p>Boost your business visibility with NYC SEO Services. Dominate local search results and attract more customers in your area. Contact us to elevate your online presence!</p><p>Boost your business visibility with our Local SEO Experts in NYC. Get found fast and attract more local customers. Optimize for success today!</p><p>Boost your NYC business with local SEO strategies to drive more traffic and attract more customers. Enhance your online presence and grow your brand today!</p><p>Boost your NYC business visibility with expert local search optimization strategies. Attract more customers and enhance your online presence in the bustling city.</p><p>Boost your NYC presence with Google My Business &amp; Local SEO services. Attract local customers and enhance visibility with expert optimization strategies.</p><p>Boost your legal practice with NYC SEO for Lawyers. Attract more clients online with expert strategies tailored for attorneys.</p><p>Boost your real estate business in NYC with effective SEO strategies tailored for agents. Enhance visibility, attract leads, and close more deals in the competitive market.</p><p>Boost your NYC online store with top-notch E-Commerce SEO. Drive traffic, increase sales, and enhance visibility with expert strategies. Skyrocket your success today!</p><p>Boost your NYC restaurants reservations with expert SEO strategies. Increase visibility, attract more diners, and enhance your online presence effectively.</p><p>Boost your NYC healthcare business with specialized SEO services. Enhance visibility, attract patients, and grow your practice through targeted digital strategies.</p><p>Boost your online visibility and rank #1 on Google with NYC SEO Experts. Achieve top search results and drive traffic to your business today!</p><p>Unlock business growth with proven NYC SEO strategies. Enhance visibility, drive traffic, and boost your brands success in the competitive New York market.</p><p>Boost your business with NYC SEO Services, driving more leads and sales through expert digital strategies tailored for success.</p><p>Boost your website traffic with NYC SEO experts. Experience tailored strategies and proven results to enhance your online presence and drive more visitors.</p><p>&quot;Boost your online presence with NYC SEO that delivers real results. Start today and see the difference. Drive traffic, enhance visibility, and grow your business!&quot;</p><p>&quot;Boost your NYC business visibility with expert technical SEO services. Optimize site structure, speed, and more to enhance search rankings and drive local traffic.&quot;</p><p>&quot;Boost rankings with NYC SEO Site Audits. Identify &amp; fix errors for enhanced visibility and performance. Elevate your sites success today!&quot;</p><p>Optimize your NYC website with speed, security, and SEO for enhanced performance and visibility. Boost user experience and search rankings effectively.</p><p>Unlock SEO success in NYC with Core Web Vitals. Enhance user experience, boost rankings, and optimize site performance for ultimate digital growth.</p><p>Boost your sites mobile performance with NYCs top SEO experts. Enhance visibility, improve rankings, and drive traffic with tailored mobile optimization strategies.</p><p>Boost your websites SEO with our high-quality link building services in NYC. Enhance visibility and drive traffic with trusted, effective strategies.</p><p>&quot;Boost your brand with NYCs top content marketing &amp; SEO services. Drive conversions and enhance visibility with strategies that deliver results.&quot;</p><p>&quot;Discover effective backlink strategies tailored for NYC businesses to boost online visibility, enhance SEO, and drive local traffic.&quot;</p><p>Engaging Blog &amp; SEO Content Writing in NYC: Elevate your brand with captivating content crafted to boost online presence and drive traffic. Lets tell your story!</p><p>Boost your business with NYC SEO Copywriting. Get persuasive, search-optimized content tailored to engage your audience and enhance your online visibility.</p><p>Boost your business visibility and outrank competitors with NYC SEO Services. Expert strategies for enhanced online presence and growth. Stay ahead today!</p><p>Affordable NYC SEO services focused on maximizing your ROI with effective strategies and results-driven solutions tailored to your business needs.</p><p>Unlock tailored NYC SEO strategies designed to boost your businesss online presence and drive growth. Get customized solutions for unique success!</p><p>Master NYC SEO strategies to outshine big brands. Boost visibility, drive traffic, and dominate search results with expert techniques tailored for competitive markets.</p><p>Boost your small business in NYC with affordable and effective SEO strategies. Enhance online visibility and attract more local customers today!</p><p>Boost your business with NYC SEO &amp; PPC! Discover the perfect digital strategy to enhance visibility, drive traffic, and maximize ROI in the competitive NYC market.</p><p>&quot;Boost your business in NYC with expert SEO &amp; Google Ads services. Drive traffic, increase visibility, and grow your brand online with our tailored strategies.&quot;</p><p>&quot;Discover the key differences between organic SEO and paid search with insights from NYC experts. Learn strategies to boost your online presence effectively.&quot;</p><p>&quot;Explore Holistic Digital Marketing in NYC: Elevate your brand with expert SEO &amp; Social Media strategies for comprehensive online growth.&quot;</p><p>Boost your NYC business with expert SEO and conversion optimization strategies. Drive traffic, increase engagement, and maximize conversions effortlessly.</p><p>&quot;Discover the top-rated NYC SEO agency trusted by businesses for boosting online presence and driving growth with proven strategies. Get results today!&quot;</p><p>Boost your online presence with New Yorks Most Trusted SEO Experts. Innovative strategies, proven results, and personalized service to elevate your business.</p><p>&quot;Expert NYC SEO team with 10+ years of experience boosting online visibility and driving growth for businesses. Results-driven strategies tailored for success.&quot;</p><p>Boost your online presence with our award-winning SEO services in NYC. Drive traffic, enhance visibility, and achieve top rankings with expert strategies.</p><p>Partner with NYCs top SEO consultants to boost your online presence, drive traffic, and achieve measurable results. Unlock your businesss digital potential today!</p><p>Boost your business with a free NYC SEO consultation. Discover tailored strategies to enhance your online presence and drive growth today!</p><p>Boost your NYC business with a comprehensive SEO audit. Enhance visibility, drive traffic, and increase revenue. Schedule now for expert insights and growth!</p><p>Boost your NYC business to the top with expert SEO strategies. Unlock page 1 rankings and maximize your online visibility. Lets get started today!</p><p>Boost your visibility with NYC SEO. Start growing your business today. Contact us now for expert SEO solutions tailored for success!</p>">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/logo.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Kumbh+Sans:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css">
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.4px!important;
font-weight: bold;
}
a:hover{
color:#ffffff;background:#ffc658!important;
}
.btn-md{
padding: 15.1px 30px;
border-radius: 0;
}
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
.a91861d3b65159c157040d46c782b112d a{
font-size:16px;
}
.xc93aa2bd24f685efae55ab6013d9a09f p,.xc93aa2bd24f685efae55ab6013d9a09f a,.xc93aa2bd24f685efae55ab6013d9a09f span,.xc93aa2bd24f685efae55ab6013d9a09f label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.nav-link{
color: #000000;

}
footer a{
color:#ffffff;
text-decoration: underline;
}
.nav-item{
padding-left:7.7px;
padding-right:7.8px;
padding-top:5.5px;
padding-bottom:5.4px;
}
.a91861d3b65159c157040d46c782b112d p,.a91861d3b65159c157040d46c782b112d span,.a91861d3b65159c157040d46c782b112d label{
font-size:16px!important;
}
footer{
background:#131313;
color:#ffffff;
}
footer *{
font-size:16px !important;
}
.a74795b93e5c2381b18ca077282658b71:hover{
box-shadow: 0 49.8px 49.5px -25px rgb(0 0 0 / 30%);
transform: rotate(-2deg) scale(1.03);
}
html{
scroll-behavior: smooth;
}
.xc93aa2bd24f685efae55ab6013d9a09f a,.a91861d3b65159c157040d46c782b112d a{
color:#0f0f0f!important;
text-decoration: underline !important;
}
.wc447a6e0df7250decee345f5a2f32b1b{
background-color:#ffc107!important;
border-color:#ffc107!important;
color:#000000!important;
}
*{
font-family: 'Kumbh Sans', sans-serif;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="index.html"  ><img alt="img/logo.jpg" src="img/logo.jpg" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span></button><div class="navbar-collapse collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="ml-auto d-flex align-items-center navbar-nav"><li class="nav-item">
<a class="d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00 nav-link" href="index.html" >Sleek Web Designs SEO Services</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00" href="nyc-seo-experts-rank-higher-grow-your-business.html" >NYC SEO Experts: Rank Higher & Grow Your Business</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00 nav-link" href="best-new-york-seo-services-for-local-national-success.html" >Best New York SEO Services for Local & National Success</a>
</li>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00" href="nycs-top-seo-agency-boost-your-online-visibility.html" >NYC’s Top SEO Agency – Boost Your Online Visibility</a>
</li>
<li class="dropdown nav-item">
<a class="dropdown-toggle d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00 nav-link" href="#" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">More</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown">
<a class="dropdown-item" href="data-driven-seo-services-in-new-york-city.html"  >Data-Driven SEO Services in New York City</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="premier-seo-solutions-for-nyc-businesses.html"  >Premier SEO Solutions for NYC Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="dominate-local-search-with-nyc-seo-services.html"  >Dominate Local Search with NYC SEO Services</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="local-seo-experts-in-nyc-get-found-fast.html"  >Local SEO Experts in NYC – Get Found Fast</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-local-seo-more-traffic-more-customers.html"  >NYC Local SEO: More Traffic, More Customers</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="optimize-your-business-for-nyc-local-search.html"  >Optimize Your Business for NYC Local Search</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="google-my-business-local-seo-services-in-nyc.html"  >Google My Business & Local SEO Services in NYC</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-seo-for-lawyers-get-more-clients-online.html"  >NYC SEO for Lawyers: Get More Clients Online</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="seo-for-real-estate-agents-in-new-york-city.html"  >SEO for Real Estate Agents in New York City</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="e-commerce-seo-in-nyc-skyrocket-your-online-store.html"  >E-Commerce SEO in NYC – Skyrocket Your Online Store</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="seo-for-nyc-restaurants-get-more-reservations.html"  >SEO for NYC Restaurants – Get More Reservations</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="healthcare-medical-seo-services-in-nyc.html"  >Healthcare & Medical SEO Services in NYC</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="rank-1-on-google-with-nyc-seo-experts.html"  >Rank #1 on Google with NYC SEO Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="proven-nyc-seo-strategies-for-business-growth.html"  >Proven NYC SEO Strategies for Business Growth</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="more-leads-sales-with-nyc-seo-services.html"  >More Leads & Sales with NYC SEO Services</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="increase-website-traffic-with-nyc-seo-professionals.html"  >Increase Website Traffic with NYC SEO Professionals</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-seo-that-drives-real-results-start-today.html"  >NYC SEO That Drives Real Results – Start Today</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="technical-seo-services-for-nyc-businesses.html"  >Technical SEO Services for NYC Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-seo-site-audits-fix-errors-rank-higher.html"  >NYC SEO Site Audits – Fix Errors & Rank Higher</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="speed-security-seo-optimize-your-nyc-website.html"  >Speed, Security & SEO: Optimize Your NYC Website</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="core-web-vitals-seo-optimization-in-nyc.html"  >Core Web Vitals & SEO Optimization in NYC</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-seo-experts-for-mobile-optimization.html"  >NYC SEO Experts for Mobile Optimization</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="high-quality-link-building-services-in-nyc.html"  >High-Quality Link Building Services in NYC</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-content-marketing-seo-that-converts.html"  >NYC Content Marketing & SEO That Converts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="backlink-strategies-for-nyc-businesses.html"  >Backlink Strategies for NYC Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="engaging-blog-seo-content-writing-in-nyc.html"  >Engaging Blog & SEO Content Writing in NYC</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-seo-copywriting-persuasive-search-optimized.html"  >NYC SEO Copywriting – Persuasive & Search-Optimized</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="stay-ahead-of-competitors-with-nyc-seo-services.html"  >Stay Ahead of Competitors with NYC SEO Services</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="affordable-nyc-seo-that-delivers-maximum-roi.html"  >Affordable NYC SEO That Delivers Maximum ROI</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="custom-nyc-seo-strategies-for-every-business.html"  >Custom NYC SEO Strategies for Every Business</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="beat-big-brands-with-nyc-seo-strategies.html"  >Beat Big Brands with NYC SEO Strategies</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-seo-for-small-businesses-affordable-effective.html"  >NYC SEO for Small Businesses – Affordable & Effective</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-seo-ppc-the-perfect-digital-strategy.html"  >NYC SEO & PPC – The Perfect Digital Strategy</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="seo-google-ads-services-in-nyc.html"  >SEO & Google Ads Services in NYC</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="organic-seo-vs-paid-search-nyc-experts-explain.html"  >Organic SEO vs. Paid Search: NYC Experts Explain</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="holistic-digital-marketing-seo-social-media-in-nyc.html"  >Holistic Digital Marketing – SEO & Social Media in NYC</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="seo-conversion-optimization-for-nyc-businesses.html"  >SEO & Conversion Optimization for NYC Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="top-rated-nyc-seo-agency-trusted-by-businesses.html"  >Top-Rated NYC SEO Agency – Trusted by Businesses</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="new-yorks-most-trusted-seo-experts.html"  >New York’s Most Trusted SEO Experts</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="nyc-seo-team-with-over-10-years-of-experience.html"  >NYC SEO Team with Over 10 Years of Experience</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="award-winning-seo-services-in-new-york-city.html"  >Award-Winning SEO Services in New York City</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="work-with-nycs-best-seo-consultants.html"  >Work with NYC’s Best SEO Consultants</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="get-a-free-nyc-seo-consultation-today.html"  >Get a Free NYC SEO Consultation Today!</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="boost-your-nyc-business-schedule-an-seo-audit.html"  >Boost Your NYC Business – Schedule an SEO Audit</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="seo-in-nyc-lets-get-your-business-on-page-1.html"  >SEO in NYC: Let’s Get Your Business on Page 1</a><a class="dropdown-item" href="start-growing-with-nyc-seo-contact-us-now.html"  >Start Growing with NYC SEO – Contact Us Now</a></div>
</li>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00 nav-link" rel=nofollow href="about-us.html">About Us</a>
</li><li class="nav-item">
<a class="wc447a6e0df7250decee345f5a2f32b1b btn btn-md" href="https://www.sleekwebdesigns.com/contact/" rel="nofollow">Contact Us</a>
</li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<section class="container" style="min-height: 80vh;">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Sleek Web Designs</h1>
<p>At Sleek Web Designs one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
 This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Sleek Web Designs and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://www.sleekwebdesigns.com/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Sleek Web Designs. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Sleek Web Designs, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Sleek Web Designs follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Sleek Web Designs.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Sleek Web Designs, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Sleek Web Designs has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Sleek Web Designs's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Sleek Web Designs does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Sleek Web Designs</br>
347) 416-5655</br>
405 Rogers Ave, Suite 101</br>
BROOKLYN</br>
New York</br>
https://www.sleekwebdesigns.com/</br>
hello@sleekwebdesigns.com</br>
</p>
</section>
<footer>
<div class="pt-5 container py-4" >
<div class="row"><div class="col-lg-3"><p><a class="d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></p>
<p><a class="d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></p>
<p><a class="d4fedb889581dc8d91b8586b7e88e4a00" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></p>
</p>
</div></div>
</div>
</footer> 
<script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script> 
</body>
</html>
